<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technical on bluehu</title>
    <link>https://huisthat.github.io/tags/technical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technical on bluehu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 17:38:50 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://huisthat.github.io/tags/technical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal Todo List Bot</title>
      <link>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/personal-todo-list-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 17:38:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/personal-todo-list-bot/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This was an individual project that is making a bot that keep tracks of the todos, deadlines and events. For deadlines and events, there will be a date and time tagged to it. It is implemented using Java, and the GUI is made using JavaFx. The jar file can be found here!
How it looks like:
Challenges One of the biggest challenges was implementing the GUI using JavaFx. I was initially really confused by the stage, scene etc, but after a few days of mulling over it, I can finally figure out how things work and get them to work as I wanted them to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphical Representation of Modules in NUS</title>
      <link>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/orbital/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 17:38:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/orbital/</guid>
      <description>Website
README
Introduction This was a pair project done over the course of three months, It was rewarding and fulfilling, as I learnt to start and complete a software development project from scratch.
Project Introduction ModPal is a graphical visualization tool for module planning. Our dynamic maps model the connections among modules in NUS, so university students can get a big picture of their academic roadmap, and visualize and explore what its curriculum coverage really means.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
