<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bluehu</title>
    <link>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bluehu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:23:50 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://huisthat.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meritocracy and Social Inequality in Singapore Education System</title>
      <link>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/meritocracy-and-social-inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:23:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/meritocracy-and-social-inequality/</guid>
      <description>This was the final paper I wrote for another USP module called Democracy and Inequality (USE2325)
It was an extremely eye opening module and I think I have learnt alot, especially about the different causes and types of inequalities. I have tried to apply my newfound knowledge and my own experiences in this paper.
Meritocracy and Social Inequality in Singapore Education System
Introduction
“Reward for Work, Work for Reward” (Poon, 2016).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Todo List Bot</title>
      <link>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/personal-todo-list-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 17:38:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/personal-todo-list-bot/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This was an individual project that is making a bot that keep tracks of the todos, deadlines and events. For deadlines and events, there will be a date and time tagged to it. It is implemented using Java, and the GUI is made using JavaFx. The jar file can be found here!
How it looks like:
Challenges One of the biggest challenges was implementing the GUI using JavaFx. I was initially really confused by the stage, scene etc, but after a few days of mulling over it, I can finally figure out how things work and get them to work as I wanted them to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphical Representation of Modules in NUS</title>
      <link>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/orbital/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 17:38:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/orbital/</guid>
      <description>Website
README
Introduction This was a pair project done over the course of three months, It was rewarding and fulfilling, as I learnt to start and complete a software development project from scratch.
Project Introduction ModPal is a graphical visualization tool for module planning. Our dynamic maps model the connections among modules in NUS, so university students can get a big picture of their academic roadmap, and visualize and explore what its curriculum coverage really means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construction Workers in Singapore</title>
      <link>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/construction-workers-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 12:23:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://huisthat.github.io/posts/construction-workers-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>This was the final paper I wrote for a USP module called Human Trafficking and Labour Migration (UWC2101F)
It may not be the best, but I was quite proud of it as it was my first time writing an actual long paper, which I would not have done if not for USP.
Construction Workers in Singapore: Their Precarious Situation and Ways to Mitigate It
Abstract
This paper examines the predicament of construction workers in Singapore, and uses Ruhs and Martin’s paper on the tradeoffs between numbers and rights of workers to explain the minimal rights the workers receive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
